<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--
 * Copyright (C) 2019 Peter Gregus for GravityBox Project (C3C076@xda)
 * Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License");
 * you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.
 * You may obtain a copy of the License at
 *
 *      http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0
 *
 * Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
 * distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS,
 * WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.
 * See the License for the specific language governing permissions and
 * limitations under the License.
-->

<resources>
    <!-- Framework -->
    <string name="config_sf_limitedAlpha">Flag indicating whether the surface flinger has limited
         alpha compositing functionality in hardware.  If set, the window
         manager will disable alpha trasformation in animations where not
         strictly needed.</string>
    <string name="config_LTE_eri_for_network_name">Use ERI text for network name on CDMA LTE</string>
    <string name="config_MaxConcurrentDownloadsAllowed">Max number of downloads allowed to proceed concurrently</string>
    <string name="config_allow3rdPartyAppOnInternal">Flag indicates that whether non-system apps can be installed on internal storage</string>
    <string name="config_allowAllRotations">If true, the screen can be rotated via the accelerometer in all 4
         rotations as the default behavior</string>
    <string name="config_allowAnimationsInLowPowerMode">This config is ued to determine whether animations are allowed in low power mode</string>
    <string name="config_allowAutoBrightnessWhileDozing">Allow automatic adjusting of the screen brightness while dozing in low power state</string>
    <string name="config_allowDisablingAssistDisclosure">Flag indicating whether the assist disclosure can be disabled using
         ASSIST_DISCLOSURE_ENABLED</string>
    <string name="config_allowPriorityVibrationsInLowPowerMode">If the device should still vibrate even in low power mode, for certain priority vibrations
     (e.g. accessibility, alarms). This is mainly for Wear devices that don\'t have speakers.</string>
    <string name="config_allowTheaterModeWakeFromCameraLens">If this is true, allow wake from theater mode from camera lens cover is switched</string>
    <string name="config_allowTheaterModeWakeFromDock">If this is true, allow wake from theater mode when docked</string>
    <string name="config_allowTheaterModeWakeFromGesture">If this is true, allow wake from theater mode from gesture</string>
    <string name="config_allowTheaterModeWakeFromKey">If this is true, allow wake from theater mode from regular key press. Setting this value to
         true implies config_allowTheaterModeWakeFromPowerKey is also true.</string>
    <string name="config_allowTheaterModeWakeFromLidSwitch">If this is true, allow wake from theater mode from lid switch</string>
    <string name="config_allowTheaterModeWakeFromMotion">If this is true, allow wake from theater mode from motion</string>
    <string name="config_allowTheaterModeWakeFromMotionWhenNotDreaming">If this is true, allow wake from theater mode from motion</string>
    <string name="config_allowTheaterModeWakeFromPowerKey">If this is true, allow wake from theater mode from power key press</string>
    <string name="config_allowTheaterModeWakeFromUnplug">If this is true, allow wake from theater mode when plugged in or unplugged</string>
    <string name="config_allowTheaterModeWakeFromWindowLayout">If this is true, allow wake from theater mode from window layout flag</string>
    <string name="config_alwaysUseCdmaRssi">Set to true if the RSSI should always display CDMA signal strength even on EVDO</string>
    <string name="config_animateScreenLights">If this is true, the screen will fade off</string>
    <string name="config_apfDrop802_3Frames">Whether the APF Filter in the device should filter out IEEE 802.3 Frames.
         Those frames are identified by the field Eth-type having values
         less than 0x600</string>
    <string name="config_autoBrightnessAmbientLightHorizon">Period of time in which to consider light samples in milliseconds</string>
    <string name="config_autoBrightnessBrighteningLightDebounce">Stability requirements in milliseconds for accepting a new brightness level.  This is used
         for debouncing the light sensor.  Different constants are used to debounce the light sensor
         when adapting to brighter or darker environments.  This parameter controls how quickly
         brightness changes occur in response to an observed change in light level that exceeds the
         hysteresis threshold.</string>
    <string name="config_autoBrightnessDarkeningLightDebounce">@string/config_autoBrightnessBrighteningLightDebounce</string>
    <string name="config_autoBrightnessInitialLightSensorRate">Initial light sensor event rate in milliseconds for automatic brightness control. This is
         used for obtaining the first light sample when the device stops dozing.
         Set this to -1 to disable this feature.</string>
    <string name="config_autoBrightnessLightSensorRate">Light sensor event rate in milliseconds for automatic brightness control</string>
    <string name="config_autoBrightnessResetAmbientLuxAfterWarmUp">When the screen is turned on, the previous estimate of the ambient light level at the time
         the screen was turned off is restored and is used to determine the initial screen
         brightness.
         If this flag is true, then the ambient light level estimate will be promptly recomputed
         after the warm-up interface and the screen brightness will be adjusted immediately.
         If this flag is false, then the ambient light level estimate will be adjusted more
         gradually in the same manner that normally happens when the screen is on according to the
         brightening or dimming debounce thresholds.  As a result, it may take somewhat longer to
         adapt to the environment. This mode may be better suited for watches.</string>
    <string name="config_autoPowerModeAnyMotionSensor">The sensor id of an "any motion" sensor used in auto-power save modes.
         0 indicates this sensor is not available.</string>
    <string name="config_autoPowerModePreferWristTilt">If an any motion sensor is not available, prefer the wrist tilt detector over the
         SMD</string>
    <string name="config_autoPowerModePrefetchLocation">If a location should be pre-fetched when going into device idle</string>
    <string name="config_autoPowerModeThresholdAngle">The threshold angle for any motion detection in auto-power save modes.
         In hundredths of a degree.</string>
    <string name="config_automatic_brightness_available">Flag indicating whether we should enable the automatic brightness in Settings.
         Software implementation will be used if config_hardware_auto_brightness_available is not set.</string>
    <string name="config_avoidGfxAccel">Device configuration indicating whether we should avoid using accelerated graphics
         in certain places to reduce RAM footprint.  This is ignored if ro.config.low_ram
         is true (in that case this is assumed true as well).  It can allow you to tune down
         your device\'s memory use without going to the point of causing applications to turn
         off features.</string>
    <string name="config_backPanicBehavior">Control the behavior when the user panic presses the back button.\n
            0 - Nothing\n
            1 - Go to home</string>
    <string name="config_bluetooth_address_validation">Boolean indicating if current platform need do one-time bluetooth address
         re-validation</string>
    <string name="config_bluetooth_default_profiles">Enable/disable default bluetooth profiles:
        HSP_AG, ObexObjectPush, Audio, NAP</string>
    <string name="config_bluetooth_hfp_inband_ringing_support">Boolean indicating if current platform supports HFP inband ringing</string>
    <string name="config_bluetooth_idle_cur_ma">Idle current for bluetooth controller</string>
    <string name="config_bluetooth_le_peripheral_mode_supported">Boolean indicating if current platform supports BLE peripheral mode</string>
    <string name="config_bluetooth_max_advertisers">Max number of advertisers supported by bluetooth controller. 0 if the
         device does not support multiple advertisement</string>
    <string name="config_bluetooth_max_scan_filters">Max number of scan filters supported by bluetooth controller. 0 if the
         device does not support hardware scan filters.</string>
    <string name="config_bluetooth_operating_voltage_mv">Operating voltage for bluetooth controller</string>
    <string name="config_bluetooth_pan_enable_autoconnect">Enables autoconnect over pan</string>
    <string name="config_bluetooth_reload_supported_profiles_when_enabled">Whether supported profiles should be reloaded upon enabling bluetooth</string>
    <string name="config_bluetooth_rx_cur_ma">Rx current for bluetooth controller</string>
    <string name="config_bluetooth_sco_off_call">Boolean indicating if current platform supports bluetooth SCO for off call
        use cases</string>
    <string name="config_bluetooth_tx_cur_ma">Tx current for bluetooth controller</string>
    <string name="config_brightness_ramp_rate_fast">Fast brightness animation ramp rate in brightness units per second</string>
    <string name="config_brightness_ramp_rate_slow">Slow brightness animation ramp rate in brightness units per second</string>
    <string name="config_built_in_sip_phone">Enables built-in SIP phone capability</string>
    <string name="config_burnInProtectionMaxHorizontalOffset">Specifies the maximum burn-in offset horizontally</string>
    <string name="config_burnInProtectionMaxRadius">Specifies the maximum burn-in offset displacement from the center. If -1, no maximum value
         will be used.</string>
    <string name="config_burnInProtectionMaxVerticalOffset">Specifies the maximum burn-in offset vertically</string>
    <string name="config_burnInProtectionMinHorizontalOffset">Specifies the minimum burn-in offset horizontally</string>
    <string name="config_burnInProtectionMinVerticalOffset">Specifies the minimum burn-in offset vertically</string>
    <string name="config_cameraDoubleTapPowerGestureEnabled">Allow the gesture to double tap the power button twice to start the camera while the device
         is non-interactive</string>
    <string name="config_cameraLaunchGestureSensorType">The OEM specified sensor type for the gesture to launch the camera app</string>
    <string name="config_cameraLiftTriggerSensorType">The OEM specified sensor type for the lift trigger to launch the camera app</string>
    <string name="config_camera_sound_forced">Whether camera shutter sound is forced or not (country specific)</string>
    <string name="config_carDockEnablesAccelerometer">Control whether being in the car dock should enable accelerometer based
         screen orientation. This defaults to true because putting a device in
         a car dock make the accelerometer more a physical input (like a lid).</string>
    <string name="config_carDockKeepsScreenOn">Control whether being in the car dock (and powered) always
         keeps the screen on.  By default it stays on when plugged in to
         AC.  0 will not keep it on; or together 1 to stay on when plugged
         in to AC and 2 to stay on when plugged in to USB.  (So 3 for both.)</string>
    <string name="config_carDockRotation">The number of degrees to rotate the display when the device is in a car dock.
         A value of -1 means no change in orientation by default.</string>
    <string name="config_carrier_volte_available">Flag specifying whether VoLTE should be available for carrier: independent of
         carrier provisioning. If false: hard disabled. If true: then depends on carrier
         provisioning, availability etc.</string>
    <string name="config_carrier_volte_tty_supported">Flag specifying whether VoLTE TTY is supported</string>
    <string name="config_carrier_vt_available">Flag specifying whether VT should be available for carrier: independent of
         carrier provisioning. If false: hard disabled. If true: then depends on carrier
         provisioning, availability etc.</string>
    <string name="config_carrier_wfc_ims_available">Flag specifying whether WFC over IMS should be available for carrier: independent of
         carrier provisioning. If false: hard disabled. If true: then depends on carrier
         provisioning, availability etc.</string>
    <string name="config_cellBroadcastAppLinks">Set to true to add links to Cell Broadcast app from Settings and MMS app</string>
    <string name="config_criticalBatteryWarningLevel">Display low battery warning when battery level dips to this value.
         Also, the battery stats are flushed to disk when we hit this level.</string>
    <string name="config_cursorWindowSize">When a database query is executed, the results retuned are paginated
         in pages of size (in KB) indicated by this value</string>
    <string name="config_customUserSwitchUi">Flag specifying whether user-switch operations have custom UI. When false, user-switch
         UI is handled by ActivityManagerService.</string>
    <string name="config_datause_polling_period_sec">The default data-use polling period</string>
    <string name="config_datause_threshold_bytes">The default data-use threshold in bytes. 0 disables.</string>
    <string name="config_datause_throttle_kbitsps">The default reduced-datarate value in kilobits per sec</string>
    <string name="config_defaultDisplayDefaultColorMode">The default mode for the default display. One of the following values (See Display.java):\n
             0 - COLOR_MODE_DEFAULT\n
             7 - COLOR_MODE_SRGB</string>
    <string name="config_defaultInTouchMode">Whether to start in touch mode</string>
    <string name="config_defaultNightDisplayAutoMode">Default mode to control how Night display is automatically activated.
         One of the following values (see NightDisplayController.java):\n
             0 - AUTO_MODE_DISABLED\n
             1 - AUTO_MODE_CUSTOM\n
             2 - AUTO_MODE_TWILIGHT</string>
    <string name="config_defaultNightDisplayCustomEndTime">Default time when Night display is automatically deactivated.
         Represented as milliseconds from midnight (e.g. 21600000 == 6am).</string>
    <string name="config_defaultNightDisplayCustomStartTime">Default time when Night display is automatically activated.
         Represented as milliseconds from midnight (e.g. 79200000 == 10pm).</string>
    <string name="config_defaultNightMode">Control the default night mode to use when there is no other mode override set.
         One of the following values (see UiModeManager.java):\n
             0 - MODE_NIGHT_AUTO\n
             1 - MODE_NIGHT_NO\n
             2 - MODE_NIGHT_YES</string>
    <string name="config_defaultNotificationLedOff">Default LED off time for notification LED in milliseconds.</string>
    <string name="config_defaultNotificationLedOn">Default LED on time for notification LED in milliseconds.</string>
    <string name="config_defaultPictureInPictureGravity">The default gravity for the picture-in-picture window.
         Currently, this maps to Gravity.BOTTOM | Gravity.RIGHT</string>
    <string name="config_defaultUiModeType">Control the default UI mode type to use when there is no other type override
         happening.  One of the following values (See Configuration.java):\n
             1  UI_MODE_TYPE_NORMAL\n
             4  UI_MODE_TYPE_TELEVISION\n
             5  UI_MODE_TYPE_APPLIANCE\n
             6  UI_MODE_TYPE_WATCH\n
             7  UI_MODE_TYPE_VR_HEADSET\n
         Any other values will have surprising consequences.</string>
    <string name="config_defaultVibrationAmplitude">The default vibration strength, must be between 1 and 255 inclusive.</string>
    <string name="config_defaultWindowFeatureContextMenu">Flags enabling default window features. See Window.java</string>
    <string name="config_defaultWindowFeatureOptionsPanel">Flags enabling default window features. See Window.java</string>
    <string name="config_deskDockEnablesAccelerometer">Control whether being in the desk dock should enable accelerometer
         based screen orientation.  This defaults to true because it is
         common for desk docks to be sold in a variety of form factors
         with different orientations.  Since we cannot always tell these docks
         apart and the docks cannot report their true orientation on their own,
         we rely on gravity to determine the effective orientation.</string>
    <string name="config_deskDockKeepsScreenOn">Control whether being in the desk dock (and powered) always
         keeps the screen on.  By default it stays on when plugged in to
         AC.  0 will not keep it on; or together 1 to stay on when plugged
         in to AC and 2 to stay on when plugged in to USB.  (So 3 for both.)</string>
    <string name="config_deskDockRotation">The number of degrees to rotate the display when the device is in a desk dock.
         A value of -1 means no change in orientation by default.</string>
    <string name="config_device_respects_hold_carrier_config">Flag specifying whether the device will use the "allow_hold_in_ims_call" carrier config
         option.  When false, the device will support holding of IMS calls, regardless of the
         carrier config setting.</string>
    <string name="config_device_volte_available">Flag specifying whether VoLTE is available on device</string>
    <string name="config_device_vt_available">Flag specifying whether VT is available on device</string>
    <string name="config_device_wfc_ims_available">Flag specifying whether WFC over IMS is available on device</string>
    <string name="config_disableLockscreenByDefault">Is the lock-screen disabled for new users by default</string>
    <string name="config_disableMenuKeyInLockScreen">Allow the menu hard key to be disabled in LockScreen on some devices </string>
    <string name="config_disableUsbPermissionDialogs">If true, then we do not ask user for permission for apps to connect to USB devices.
         Do not set this to true for production devices. Doing so will cause you to fail CTS.</string>
    <string name="config_displayBlanksAfterDoze">Whether the display blanks itself when transitioning from a doze to a non-doze state</string>
    <string name="config_displayBrightnessBucketsInDoze">True if the display hardware only has brightness buckets rather than a full range of
         backlight values</string>
    <string name="config_dockedStackDividerSnapMode">Controls the snap mode for the docked stack divider\n
             0 - 3 snap targets: left/top has 16:9 ratio, 1:1, and right/bottom has 16:9 ratio\n
             1 - 3 snap targets: fixed ratio, 1:1, (1 - fixed ratio)\n
             2 - 1 snap target: 1:1</string>
    <string name="config_dontPreferApn">Set to true if we need to not prefer an APN.
         This is being added to enable a simple scenario of pre-paid
         provisioning on some carriers, working around a bug (7305641)
         where if the preferred is used we don\'t try the others.</string>
    <string name="config_doublePressOnPowerBehavior">Control the behavior when the user double presses the power button.\n
            0 - Nothing\n
            1 - Toggle theater mode setting\n
            2 - Brightness boost</string>
    <string name="config_doubleTapOnHomeBehavior">Control the behavior when the user double-taps the home button.\n
            0 - Nothing\n
            1 - Recent apps view in SystemUI\n
         This needs to match the constants in
         policy/src/com/android/internal/policy/impl/PhoneWindowManager.java</string>
    <string name="config_downloadDataDirLowSpaceThreshold">When the free space available in DownloadManager\'s data dir falls
         below the percentage value specified by this param, DownloadManager
         starts removing files to try to make percentage of available
         free space above this threshold value.</string>
    <string name="config_downloadDataDirSize">Max space (in MB) allocated to DownloadManager to store the downloaded
         files if they are to be stored in DownloadManager\'s data dir,
         which typically is /data/data/com.android.providers.downloads/files</string>
    <string name="config_dozeAfterScreenOff">If true, the doze component is not started until after the screen has been
         turned off and the screen off animation has been performed.</string>
    <string name="config_dozeAlwaysOnDisplayAvailable">Control whether the always on display mode is available. This should only be enabled on
         devices where the display has be tuned to be power efficient in DOZE and/or DOZE_SUSPEND
         states.</string>
    <string name="config_dozePulsePickup">Doze: should the TYPE_PICK_UP_GESTURE sensor be used as a pulse signal.</string>
    <string name="config_drawLockTimeoutMillis">Number of milliseconds to hold a wake lock to ensure that drawing is fully
         flushed to the display while dozing.  This value needs to be large enough
         to account for processing and rendering time plus a frame or two of latency
         in the display pipeline plus some slack just to be sure.</string>
    <string name="config_dreamsActivatedOnDockByDefault">If supported and enabled, are dreams activated when docked? (by default)</string>
    <string name="config_dreamsActivatedOnSleepByDefault">If supported and enabled, are dreams activated when asleep and charging? (by default)</string>
    <string name="config_dreamsBatteryLevelDrainCutoff">If the battery level drops by this percentage and the user activity timeout
         has expired, then assume the device is receiving insufficient current to charge
         effectively and terminate the dream.  Use -1 to disable this safety feature.</string>
    <string name="config_dreamsBatteryLevelMinimumWhenNotPowered">Minimum battery level to allow dreaming when not powered.
         Use -1 to disable this safety feature.</string>
    <string name="config_dreamsBatteryLevelMinimumWhenPowered">Minimum battery level to allow dreaming when powered.
         Use -1 to disable this safety feature.</string>
    <string name="config_dreamsEnabledByDefault">If supported, are dreams enabled? (by default)</string>
    <string name="config_dreamsEnabledOnBattery">Are we allowed to dream while not plugged in?</string>
    <string name="config_dreamsSupported">Specifies whether the dreams feature should be supported.
         When true, the system will allow the user to configure dreams (screensavers)
         to launch when a user activity timeout occurs or the system is told to nap.
         When false, the dreams feature will be disabled (this does not affect dozing).
         Consider setting this resource to false or disabling dreams by default when a
         doze component is specified below since dreaming will supercede dozing and
         will prevent the system from entering a low power state until the dream ends.</string>
    <string name="config_duplicate_port_omadm_wappush">If this value is true, duplicate Source/Destination port fields
         in WDP header of some carriers OMADM wap push are supported.
         ex: MSGTYPE-TotalSegments-CurrentSegment
             -SourcePortDestPort-SourcePortDestPort-OMADM PDU
         If false, not supported.</string>
    <string name="config_dynamic_bind_ims">Flag specifying whether or not IMS will use the dynamic ImsResolver</string>
    <string name="config_eap_sim_based_auth_supported">Flag indicating device support for EAP SIM, AKA, AKA\'</string>
    <string name="config_enableActivityRecognitionHardwareOverlay">Whether to enable Hardware Activity-Recognition overlay which allows Hardware
         Activity-Recognition to be replaced by an app at run-time. When disabled, only the
         config_activityRecognitionHardwarePackageName package will be searched for
         its implementation, otherwise packages whose signature matches the
         signatures of config_locationProviderPackageNames will be searched, and
         the service with the highest version number will be picked. Anyone who
         wants to disable the overlay mechanism can set it to false.</string>
    <string name="config_enableAppWidgetService">True if the device requires AppWidgetService even if it does not have
         the PackageManager.FEATURE_APP_WIDGETS feature</string>
    <string name="config_enableAutoPowerModes">Set this to true to enable the platform\'s auto-power-save modes like doze and
         app standby.  These are not enabled by default because they require a standard
         cloud-to-device messaging service for apps to interact correctly with the modes
         (such as to be able to deliver an instant message to the device even when it is
         dozing).  This should be enabled if you have such services and expect apps to
         correctly use them when installed on your device.  Otherwise, keep this disabled
         so that applications can still use their own mechanisms.</string>
    <string name="config_enableBurnInProtection">If true, the display will be shifted around in ambient mode</string>
    <string name="config_enableCarDockHomeLaunch">Control whether to launch Car dock home app when user presses home button or when
          car dock intent is fired.
          In mobile device, usually separate home app is expected in car mode, and this should be
          enabled. But in environments like real car, default home app may be enough, and in that
          case, this can be disabled (set to false).</string>
    <string name="config_enableCredentialFactoryResetProtection">If true, enables verification of the lockscreen credential in the factory reset protection
        flow. This should be true if gatekeeper / weaver credentials can still be checked after a
        factory reset.</string>
    <string name="config_enableHapticTextHandle">Enables or disables haptic effect when the text insertion/selection handle is moved
         manually by the user. Off by default, since the expected haptic feedback may not be
         available on some devices.</string>
    <string name="config_enableLockBeforeUnlockScreen">Whether to show lock screen before unlock screen (PIN/pattern/password)</string>
    <string name="config_enableLockScreenRotation">Enables/disables lock screen rotation</string>
    <string name="config_enableLockScreenTranslucentDecor">Enables/disables lockscreen translucent decor</string>
    <string name="config_enableMultiUserUI">Whether UI for multi user should be shown</string>
    <string name="config_enableNightMode">Flag indicating whether or not to enable night mode detection.</string>
    <string name="config_enableScreenshotChord">If this is true, key chords can be used to take a screenshot on the device.</string>
    <string name="config_enableTranslucentDecor">Enables/disables translucent decor</string>
    <string name="config_enableUpdateableTimeZoneRules">Enables the TimeZoneRuleManager service. This is the master switch for the updateable time
         zone update mechanism.</string>
    <string name="config_enableWallpaperService">Enables/disables WallpaperService</string>
    <string name="config_enableWifiDisplay">Whether WiFi display is supported by this device.
         There are many prerequisites for this feature to work correctly.
         Here are a few of them:\n
         * The WiFi radio must support WiFi P2P.\n
         * The WiFi radio must support concurrent connections to the WiFi display and
           to an access point.\n
         * The Audio Flinger audio_policy.conf file must specify a rule for the "r_submix"
           remote submix module.  This module is used to record and stream system
           audio output to the WiFi display encoder in the media server.\n
         * The remote submix module "audio.r_submix.default" must be installed on the device.\n
         * The device must be provisioned with HDCP keys (for protected content).</string>
    <string name="config_enable_emergency_call_while_sim_locked">Enable emergency call when sim is locked or puk locked. Some countries/carriers do not
         allow emergency calls to be placed without the IMSI, which is locked in the SIM.
         If so, this should be set to \'false\' in an overlay.</string>
    <string name="config_enable_puk_unlock_screen">Enable puk unlockscreen by default.
         If unlock screen is disabled, the puk should be unlocked through Emergency Dialer</string>
    <string name="config_externalHardKeyboardBehavior">Controls how we deal with externally connected physical keyboards.\n
         0 - When using this device, it is not clear for users to recognize when the physical
             keyboard is (should be) connected and when it is (should be) disconnected.  Most of
             phones and tablets with Bluetooth keyboard would fall into this category because the
             connected Bluetooth keyboard may or may not be nearby the host device.\n
         1 - When using this device, it is clear for users to recognize when the physical
             keyboard is (should be) connected and when it is (should be) disconnected.
             Devices with wired USB keyboard is one clear example.  Some 2-in-1 convertible
             tablets with dedicated keyboards may have the same affordance to wired USB keyboard.</string>
    <string name="config_extraFreeKbytesAbsolute">Device configuration setting the /proc/sys/vm/extra_free_kbytes tunable in the kernel
         (if it exists).  A high value will increase the amount of memory that the kernel
         tries to keep free, reducing allocation time and causing the lowmemorykiller to kill
         earlier.  A low value allows more memory to be used by processes but may cause more
         allocations to block waiting on disk I/O or lowmemorykiller.  Overrides the default
         value chosen by ActivityManager based on screen size.  0 prevents keeping any extra
         memory over what the kernel keeps by default.  -1 keeps the default.</string>
    <string name="config_extraFreeKbytesAdjust">Device configuration adjusting the /proc/sys/vm/extra_free_kbytes tunable in the kernel
         (if it exists).  0 uses the default value chosen by ActivityManager.  A positive value
         will increase the amount of memory that the kernel tries to keep free, reducing
         allocation time and causing the lowmemorykiller to kill earlier.  A negative value
         allows more memory to be used by processes but may cause more allocations to block
         waiting on disk I/O or lowmemorykiller.  Directly added to the default value chosen by
         ActivityManager based on screen size.</string>
    <string name="config_fingerprintMaxTemplatesPerUser">For performance and storage reasons, limit the number of fingerprints per user</string>
    <string name="config_forceDefaultOrientation">Flag indicating that this device does not rotate and will always remain in its default
         orientation. Activities that desire to run in a non-compatible orientation will be run
         from an emulated display within the physical display.</string>
    <string name="config_forceWindowDrawsStatusBarBackground">If set, this will force all windows to draw the status bar background, including the apps
         that have not requested doing so (via the WindowManager.FLAG_DRAWS_SYSTEM_BAR_BACKGROUNDS
         flag).</string>
    <string name="config_freeformWindowManagement">The device supports freeform window management. Windows have title bars and can be moved
         and resized. If you set this to true, you also need to add
         PackageManager.FEATURE_FREEFORM_WINDOW_MANAGEMENT feature to your device specification.
         The duplication is necessary, because this information is used before the features are
         available to the system.</string>
    <string name="config_globalActionsKeyTimeout">Amount of time in ms the user needs to press the relevant key to bring up the global actions dialog</string>
    <string name="config_goToSleepOnButtonPressTheaterMode">If this is true, go to sleep when theater mode is enabled from button press</string>
    <string name="config_guestUserEphemeral">If true, all guest users created on the device will be ephemeral.</string>
    <string name="config_handleVolumeKeysInWindowManager">Handle volume keys directly in Window Manager without passing them to the foreground app</string>
    <string name="config_hasPermanentDpad">Override the DPad detection behavior for configuration purposes</string>
    <string name="config_hasRecents">Default device has recents property</string>
    <string name="config_hotswapCapable">Is the device capable of hot swapping an UICC Card</string>
    <string name="config_immersive_mode_confirmation_panic">Threshold (in ms) under which a screen off / screen on will be considered a reset of the
         immersive mode confirmation prompt.</string>
    <string name="config_intrusiveNotificationLed">Is the notification LED intrusive? Used to decide if there should be a disable option</string>
    <string name="config_jobSchedulerIdleWindowSlop">The alarm window (in milliseconds) that JobScheduler uses to enter the idle state</string>
    <string name="config_jobSchedulerInactivityIdleThreshold">Inactivity threshold (in milliseconds) used in JobScheduler. JobScheduler will consider
         the device to be "idle" after being inactive for this long.</string>
    <string name="config_keepPreloadsMinDays">Number of days preloaded file cache should be preserved on a device before it can be
         deleted</string>
    <string name="config_lidControlsScreenLock">Indicate whether closing the lid causes the lockscreen to appear.
         The default is false.</string>
    <string name="config_lidControlsSleep">Indicate whether closing the lid causes the device to go to sleep and opening
         it causes the device to wake up.
         The default is false.</string>
    <string name="config_lidKeyboardAccessibility">Indicate whether the lid state impacts the accessibility of
         the physical keyboard.  0 means it doesn\'t, 1 means it is accessible
         when the lid is open, 2 means it is accessible when the lid is
         closed.  The default is 0.</string>
    <string name="config_lidNavigationAccessibility">Indicate whether the lid state impacts the accessibility of
         the navigation buttons.  0 means it doesn\'t, 1 means it is accessible
         when the lid is open, 2 means it is accessible when the lid is
         closed.  The default is 0.</string>
    <string name="config_lidOpenRotation">The number of degrees to rotate the display when the keyboard is open.
         A value of -1 means no change in orientation by default.</string>
    <string name="config_lightSensorWarmupTime">Amount of time it takes for the light sensor to warm up in milliseconds.
         For this time after the screen turns on, the Power Manager
         will not debounce light sensor readings</string>
    <string name="config_localDisplaysMirrorContent">When true, local displays that do not contain any of their own content will automatically
         mirror the content of the default display.</string>
    <string name="config_lockDayNightMode">Control whether to lock day/night mode change from normal application. When it is
          true, day / night mode change is only allowed to apps with MODIFY_DAY_NIGHT_MODE
          permission.</string>
    <string name="config_lockSoundVolumeDb">The attenuation in dB applied to the lock/unlock sounds</string>
    <string name="config_lockUiMode">Control whether to lock UI mode to what is selected from config_defaultUiModeType.
          Once UI mode is locked, applications cannot change it anymore.</string>
    <string name="config_longAnimTime">The duration (in milliseconds) of a long animation.</string>
    <string name="config_longPressOnBackBehavior">Control the behavior when the user long presses the back button.  Non-zero values are only
         valid for watches as part of CDD/CTS.\n
            0 - Nothing\n
            1 - Go to voice assist</string>
    <string name="config_longPressOnHomeBehavior">Control the behavior when the user long presses the home button.\n
            0 - Nothing\n
            1 - Launch all apps intent\n
            2 - Launch assist intent\n
         This needs to match the constants in
         policy/src/com/android/internal/policy/impl/PhoneWindowManager.java</string>
    <string name="config_longPressOnPowerBehavior">Control the behavior when the user long presses the power button.\n
            0 - Nothing\n
            1 - Global actions menu\n
            2 - Power off (with confirmation)\n
            3 - Power off (without confirmation)</string>
    <string name="config_lowBatteryCloseWarningBump">Close low battery warning when battery level reaches the lowBatteryWarningLevel
         plus this</string>
    <string name="config_lowBatteryWarningLevel">Display low battery warning when battery level dips to this value</string>
    <string name="config_lowMemoryKillerMinFreeKbytesAbsolute">Device configuration setting the minfree tunable in the lowmemorykiller in the kernel.
         A high value will cause the lowmemorykiller to fire earlier, keeping more memory
         in the file cache and preventing I/O thrashing, but allowing fewer processes to
         stay in memory.  A low value will keep more processes in memory but may cause
         thrashing if set too low.  Overrides the default value chosen by ActivityManager
         based on screen size and total memory for the largest lowmemorykiller bucket, and
         scaled proportionally to the smaller buckets.  -1 keeps the default.</string>
    <string name="config_lowMemoryKillerMinFreeKbytesAdjust">Device configuration adjusting the minfree tunable in the lowmemorykiller in the
         kernel.  A high value will cause the lowmemorykiller to fire earlier, keeping more
         memory in the file cache and preventing I/O thrashing, but allowing fewer processes
         to stay in memory.  A low value will keep more processes in memory but may cause
         thrashing if set too low.  Directly added to the default value chosen by
         ActivityManager based on screen size and total memory for the largest lowmemorykiller
         bucket, and scaled proportionally to the smaller buckets. 0 keeps the default. </string>
    <string name="config_mainBuiltInDisplayIsRound">Whether the main built-in display is round. This will affect
         Configuration.screenLayout\'s SCREENLAYOUT_ROUND_MASK flags for Configurations on the
         main built-in display. Change this in device-specific overlays.
         Defaults to the older, deprecated config_windowIsRound already used in
         some existing device-specific resource overlays.</string>
    <string name="config_maxResolverActivityColumns">Maximum number of grid columns permitted in the ResolverActivity
         used for picking activities to handle an intent.</string>
    <string name="config_maxUiWidth">Maximum size, specified in pixels, to restrain the display space width to. Height and
         density will be scaled accordingly to maintain aspect ratio. A value of 0 indicates no
         constraint will be enforced.</string>
    <string name="config_max_pan_devices">Max number of Bluetooth tethering connections allowed. If this is
         updated config_tether_dhcp_range has to be updated appropriately.</string>
    <string name="config_maximumScreenDimDuration">User activity timeout: Maximum screen dim duration in milliseconds.
         Sets an upper bound for how long the screen will dim before the device goes
         to sleep when there is no user activity.  The dim duration is subtracted from
         the overall screen off timeout to determine the screen dim timeout.
         When the screen dim timeout expires, the screen will dim, shortly thereafter
         the device will go to sleep.
         If the screen off timeout is very short, the dim duration may be reduced
         proportionally.  See config_maximumScreenDimRatio.
         This value may be zero in which case the screen will not dim before the
         device goes to sleep.</string>
    <string name="config_mdc_initial_max_retry">Set initial MaxRetry value for operators</string>
    <string name="config_mediumAnimTime">The duration (in milliseconds) of a medium-length animation</string>
    <string name="config_minimumScreenOffTimeout">User activity timeout: Minimum screen off timeout in milliseconds.
         Sets a lower bound for the {@link Settings.System#SCREEN_OFF_TIMEOUT} setting
         which determines how soon the device will go to sleep when there is no
         user activity.
         This value must be greater than zero, otherwise the device will immediately
         fall asleep again as soon as it is awoken.</string>
    <string name="config_mms_content_disposition_support">If this value is true, The mms content-disposition field is supported correctly.
         If false, Content-disposition fragments are ignored</string>
    <string name="config_mobile_hotspot_provision_check_period">Number of hours between each background provisioning call</string>
    <string name="config_mobile_mtu">Configure mobile network MTU</string>
    <string name="config_multiuserMaximumUsers">Maximum number of supported users</string>
    <string name="config_navBarOpacityMode">Controls the opacity of the navigation bar depending on the visibility of the
         various workspace stacks.\n
         0 - Nav bar is always opaque when either the freeform stack or docked stack is visible.\n
         1 - Nav bar is always translucent when the freeform stack is visible, otherwise always
         opaque.</string>
    <string name="config_networkAvoidBadWifi">Whether the device should automatically switch away from Wi-Fi networks that lose
         Internet access. Actual device behaviour is controlled by
         Settings.Global.NETWORK_AVOID_BAD_WIFI.</string>
    <string name="config_networkMeteredMultipathPreference">Default value for ConnectivityManager.getMultipathPreference() on metered networks. Actual
         device behaviour is controlled by Settings.Global.NETWORK_METERED_MULTIPATH_PREFERENCE.</string>
    <string name="config_networkNotifySwitchType">Whether/how to notify the user on network switches. See LingerMonitor.java.</string>
    <string name="config_networkTransitionTimeout">The maximum duration (in milliseconds) we expect a network transition to take</string>
    <string name="config_networkWakeupPacketMark">If the hardware supports specially marking packets that caused a wakeup of the
         main CPU, set this value to the mark used.</string>
    <string name="config_networkWakeupPacketMask">Mask to use when checking skb mark defined in config_networkWakeupPacketMark</string>
    <string name="config_nightDisplayAvailable">Control whether Night display is available. This should only be enabled on devices
         that have a HWC implementation that can apply the matrix passed to setColorTransform
         without impacting power, performance, and app compatibility (e.g. protected content).</string>
    <string name="config_nightDisplayColorTemperatureDefault">Default color temperature, in Kelvin, to tint the screen when Night display is
         activated.</string>
    <string name="config_nightDisplayColorTemperatureMax">Maximum color temperature, in Kelvin, supported by Night display</string>
    <string name="config_nightDisplayColorTemperatureMin">Minimum color temperature, in Kelvin, supported by Night display</string>
    <string name="config_noHomeScreen">True if the device has no home screen. That is a launcher activity
         where the user can launch other applications from.</string>
    <string name="config_notificationBadging">De we do icon badges? Used to decide if there should be a disable option</string>
    <string name="config_notificationHeaderClickableForExpand">Flag indicating that the entire notification header can be clicked to expand the
         notification. If false, then the expand icon has to be clicked in order for the expand
         to occur. The expand button will have increased touch boundaries to accommodate this.</string>
    <string name="config_notificationServiceArchiveSize">Number of notifications to keep in the notification service historical archive</string>
    <string name="config_notificationsBatteryFullARGB">Default value for led color when battery is fully charged</string>
    <string name="config_notificationsBatteryLedOff">Default value for LED off time when the battery is low on charge in miliseconds</string>
    <string name="config_notificationsBatteryLedOn">Default value for LED on time when the battery is low on charge in miliseconds</string>
    <string name="config_notificationsBatteryLowARGB">Default value for led color when battery is low on charge</string>
    <string name="config_notificationsBatteryMediumARGB">Default value for led color when battery is medium charged</string>
    <string name="config_ntpPollingInterval">Normal NTP polling frequency in milliseconds</string>
    <string name="config_ntpPollingIntervalShorter">Try-again NTP polling interval in milliseconds, in case the network request failed</string>
    <string name="config_ntpRetry">Number of times to try again with the shorter interval, before backing
         off until the normal NTP polling interval. A value &lt; 0 indicates infinite.</string>
    <string name="config_ntpThreshold">If the time difference is greater than this threshold in milliseconds,
         then update the time.</string>
    <string name="config_ntpTimeout">Timeout to wait for NTP server response in milliseconds</string>
    <string name="config_overrideHasPermanentMenuKey">Override the default detection behavior for the framework method
         android.view.ViewConfiguration#hasPermanentMenuKey().
         Valid settings are:\n
         0 - No change. Use the default autodetection behavior.\n
         1 - The device DOES have a permanent menu key; ignore autodetection.\n
         2 - The device DOES NOT have a permanent menu key; ignore autodetection.</string>
    <string name="config_overrideRemoteViewsActivityTransition">If true, the transition for a RemoteViews is read from a resource instead of using the
         default scale-up transition</string>
    <string name="config_permissionReviewRequired">Specifies whether the permissions needed by a legacy app should be
         reviewed before any of its components can run. A legacy app is one
         with targetSdkVersion &lt; 23, i.e apps using the old permission model.
         If review is not required, permissions are reviewed before the app
         is installed.</string>
    <string name="config_pictureInPictureSnapMode">The snap mode to use for picture-in-picture. These values correspond to constants defined
         in PipSnapAlgorithm and should not be changed independently.\n
             0 - Snap to the four corners\n
             1 - Snap to the four corners and the mid-points on the long edge in each orientation\n
             2 - Snap anywhere along the edge of the screen\n
             3 - Snap anywhere along the edge of the screen and magnet to corners\n
             4 - Snap to the long edges in each orientation and magnet to corners</string>
    <string name="config_pinnerCameraApp">True if camera app should be pinned via Pinner Service</string>
    <string name="config_powerDecoupleAutoSuspendModeFromDisplay">Power Management: Specifies whether to decouple the auto-suspend state of the
         device from the display on/off state.
         When false, autosuspend_disable() will be called before the display is turned on
         and autosuspend_enable() will be called after the display is turned off.
         This mode provides best compatibility for devices using legacy power management
         features such as early suspend / late resume.
         When true, autosuspend_display() and autosuspend_enable() will be called
         independently of whether the display is being turned on or off.  This mode
         enables the power manager to suspend the application processor while the
         display is on.
         This resource should be set to "true" when a doze component has been specified
         to maximize power savings but not all devices support it.
         Refer to autosuspend.h for details.</string>
    <string name="config_powerDecoupleInteractiveModeFromDisplay">Power Management: Specifies whether to decouple the interactive state of the
         device from the display on/off state.
         When false, setInteractive(…, true) will be called before the display is turned on
         and setInteractive(…, false) will be called after the display is turned off.
         This mode provides best compatibility for devices that expect the interactive
         state to be tied to the display state.
         When true, setInteractive(…) will be called independently of whether the display
         is being turned on or off.  This mode enables the power manager to reduce
         clocks and disable the touch controller while the display is on.
         This resource should be set to "true" when a doze component has been specified
         to maximize power savings but not all devices support it.
         Refer to power.h for details.</string>
    <string name="config_previousVibrationsDumpLimit">How long history of previous vibrations should be kept for the dumpsys</string>
    <string name="config_quickSettingsSupported">Whether the device supports quick settings and its associated APIs</string>
    <string name="config_radioScanningTimeout">The duration (in milliseconds) that the radio will scan for a signal
         when there\'s no network connection. If the scan doesn\'t timeout, use zero</string>
    <string name="config_requireCallCapableAccountForHandle">Flag indicating that an outbound call must have a call capable phone account
         that has declared it can process the call\'s handle</string>
    <string name="config_requireRadioPowerOffOnSimRefreshReset">Boolean indicating if RADIO POWER OFF is required on receiving SIM REFRESH with RESET.
         This will be handled by modem if it is false.</string>
    <string name="config_restartRadioAfterProvisioning">Set to true if after a provisioning apn the radio should be restarted</string>
    <string name="config_restart_radio_on_pdp_fail_regular_deactivation">Flag indicating whether radio is to be restarted on the error of
         PDP_FAIL_REGULAR_DEACTIVATION/0x24</string>
    <string name="config_reverseDefaultRotation">If true, the direction rotation is applied to get to an application\'s requested
         orientation is reversed.  Normally, the model is that landscape is
         clockwise from portrait; thus on a portrait device an app requesting
         landscape will cause a clockwise rotation, and on a landscape device an
         app requesting portrait will cause a counter-clockwise rotation.  Setting
         true here reverses that logic.</string>
    <string name="config_safe_media_volume_enabled">Whether safe headphone volume is enabled or not (country specific)</string>
    <string name="config_safe_media_volume_index">Safe headphone volume index. When music stream volume is below this index
        the SPL on headphone output is compliant to EN 60950 requirements for portable music
        players.</string>
    <string name="config_screenBrightnessDark">Minimum allowable screen brightness to use in a very dark room.
         This value sets the floor for the darkest possible auto-brightness
         adjustment.  It is expected to be somewhat less than the first entry in
         config_autoBrightnessLcdBacklightValues so as to allow the user to have
         some range of adjustment to dim the screen further than usual in very
         dark rooms. The contents of the screen must still be clearly visible
         in darkness (although they may not be visible in a bright room).</string>
    <string name="config_screenBrightnessDim">Screen brightness used to dim the screen when the user activity
         timeout expires.  May be less than the minimum allowed brightness setting
         that can be set by the user.</string>
    <string name="config_screenBrightnessDoze">Screen brightness used to dim the screen while dozing in a very low power state.
         May be less than the minimum allowed brightness setting
         that can be set by the user.</string>
    <string name="config_screenBrightnessForVrSettingDefault">Default screen brightness for VR setting</string>
    <string name="config_screenBrightnessForVrSettingMaximum">Maximum screen brightness setting allowed for VR</string>
    <string name="config_screenBrightnessForVrSettingMinimum">Minimum screen brightness setting allowed for VR. Device panels start increasing pulse
         width as brightness decreases below this theshold.</string>
    <string name="config_screenBrightnessSettingDefault">Default screen brightness setting.
         Must be in the range specified by minimum and maximum.</string>
    <string name="config_screenBrightnessSettingMaximum">Maximum screen brightness allowed by the power manager.
         The user is forbidden from setting the brightness above this level.</string>
    <string name="config_screenBrightnessSettingMinimum">Minimum screen brightness setting allowed by the power manager.
         The user is forbidden from setting the brightness below this level.</string>
    <string name="config_screen_magnification_multi_tap_adjustment">Time adjustment, in milliseconds, applied to the default double tap threshold
         used for gesture detection by the screen magnifier.</string>
    <string name="config_sendAudioBecomingNoisy">Flag indicating whether the AUDIO_BECOMING_NOISY notification should
         be sent during a change to the audio output device</string>
    <string name="config_sendPackageName">Whether to send a custom package name with the PSD</string>
    <string name="config_setColorTransformAccelerated">Boolean indicating whether the HWC setColorTransform function can be performed efficiently
         in hardware</string>
    <string name="config_shortAnimTime">The duration (in milliseconds) of a short animation</string>
    <string name="config_shortPressOnPowerBehavior">Control the behavior when the user short presses the power button.\n
            0 - Nothing\n
            1 - Go to sleep (doze)\n
            2 - Really go to sleep (don\'t doze)\n
            3 - Really go to sleep and go home (don\'t doze)\n
            4 - Go to home\n
            5 - Dismiss IME if shown. Otherwise go to home</string>
    <string name="config_shortPressOnSleepBehavior">Control the behavior when the user presses the sleep button.\n
            0 - Go to sleep (doze)\n
            1 - Go to sleep (doze) and go home</string>
    <string name="config_showAreaUpdateInfoSettings">Show area update info settings in CellBroadcastReceiver and information in SIM status in Settings app</string>
    <string name="config_showMenuShortcutsWhenKeyboardPresent">Sets whether menu shortcuts should be displayed on panel menus when
         a keyboard is present</string>
    <string name="config_showNavigationBar">Whether a software navigation bar should be shown. NOTE: in the future this may be
         autodetected from the Configuration.</string>
    <string name="config_showSysuiShutdown">Allow SystemUI to show the shutdown dialog</string>
    <string name="config_shutdownBatteryTemperature">Shutdown if the battery temperature exceeds (this value * 0.1) Celsius</string>
    <string name="config_single_volume">Flag indicating whether all audio streams should be mapped to
         one single stream. If true, all audio streams are mapped to
         STREAM_MUSIC as if it\'s on TV platform.</string>
    <string name="config_sip_wifi_only">Enables SIP on WIFI only</string>
    <string name="config_skipScreenOnBrightnessRamp">Whether or not to skip the initial brightness ramps when the display transitions to
         STATE_ON. Setting this to true will skip the brightness ramp to the last stored active
         brightness value and will repeat for the following ramp if autobrightness is enabled.</string>
    <string name="config_sms_capable">Flag indicating whether the current device allows sms service.
         If true, this means that the device supports both sending and
         receiving sms via the telephony network.
         This can be overridden to false for "data only" devices
         which can\'t send and receive sms message.
         Note: Disable SMS also disable voicemail waiting sms,
               cell broadcasting sms, and MMS.</string>
    <string name="config_sms_decode_gsm_8bit_data">Support decoding the user data payload as pack GSM 8-bit (a GSM alphabet
        string that\'s stored in 8-bit unpacked format) characters.</string>
    <string name="config_sms_utf8_support">If this value is true, Sms encoded as octet is decoded by utf8 decoder.
         If false, decoded by Latin decoder.</string>
    <string name="config_soundEffectVolumeDb">The attenuation in dB applied to the sound effects played
         through AudioManager.playSoundEffect() when no volume is specified</string>
    <string name="config_speed_up_audio_on_mt_calls">Flag indicating if the speed up audio on mt call code should be executed</string>
    <string name="config_stableDeviceDisplayHeight">The stable device height in pixels. If it isn\'t set to a positive number
         then the device will use the height of the default display the first time it\'s
         booted.</string>
    <string name="config_stableDeviceDisplayWidth">The stable device width in pixels. If it isn\'t set to a positive number
         then the device will use the width of the default display the first time it\'s
         booted.</string>
    <string name="config_stkNoAlphaUsrCnf">Set to false if we need to show user confirmation
         when alpha identifier is not provided by the UICC</string>
    <string name="config_storageManagerDaystoRetainDefault">Default number of days to retain for the automatic storage manager</string>
    <string name="config_strongAuthRequiredOnBoot">Enforce strong auth on boot. Setting this to false represents a security risk and should
         not be ordinarily done. The only case in which this might be permissible is in a car head
         unit where there are hardware mechanisms to protect the device (physical keys) and not
         much in the way of user data.</string>
    <string name="config_supportAudioSourceUnprocessed">Whether the Unprocessed audio source supports the required frequency range and level</string>
    <string name="config_supportAutoRotation">If true, enables auto-rotation features using the accelerometer.
         Otherwise, auto-rotation is disabled.  Applications may still request
         to use specific orientations but the sensor is ignored and sensor-based
         orientations are not available.  Furthermore, all auto-rotation related
         settings are omitted from the system UI.  In certain situations we may
         still use the accelerometer to determine the orientation, such as when
         docked if the dock is configured to enable the accelerometer.</string>
    <string name="config_supportDoubleTapWake">Whether device supports double tap to wake</string>
    <string name="config_supportLongPressPowerWhenNonInteractive">If this is true, long press on power button will be available from the non-interactive state</string>
    <string name="config_supportMicNearUltrasound">Whether the default microphone audio source supports near-ultrasound frequencies
         (range of 18 - 21 kHz)</string>
    <string name="config_supportPreRebootSecurityLogs">True if the device supports persisting security logs across reboots.
         This requires the device\'s kernel to have pstore and pmsg enabled,
         and DRAM to be powered and refreshed through all stages of reboot.</string>
    <string name="config_supportSpeakerNearUltrasound">Whether the default speaker audio output path supports near-ultrasound frequencies
         (range of 18 - 21 kHz)</string>
    <string name="config_supportSystemNavigationKeys">True if the device supports system navigation keys</string>
    <string name="config_supportsMultiDisplay">True if the device supports running activities on secondary displays</string>
    <string name="config_supportsMultiWindow">True if the device supports at least one form of multi-window.
         E.g. freeform, split-screen, picture-in-picture.</string>
    <string name="config_supportsSplitScreenMultiWindow">True if the device supports split screen as a form of multi-window</string>
    <string name="config_suspendWhenScreenOffDueToProximity">Indicate whether to allow the device to suspend when the screen is off
         due to the proximity sensor.  This resource should only be set to true
         if the sensor HAL correctly handles the proximity sensor as a wake-up source.
         Otherwise, the device may fail to wake out of suspend reliably.
         The default is false.</string>
    <string name="config_sustainedPerformanceModeSupported">True if the device supports Sustained Performance Mode</string>
    <string name="config_swipeDisambiguation">Enables swipe versus poly-finger touch disambiguation in the KeyboardView</string>
    <string name="config_switch_phone_on_voice_reg_state_change">Config determines whether to update phone object when voice registration
         state changes. Voice radio tech change will always trigger an update of
         phone object irrespective of this config</string>
    <string name="config_syncstorageengine_masterSyncAutomatically">The default value if the SyncStorageEngine should sync automatically or not</string>
    <string name="config_telephony_use_own_number_for_voicemail">The VoiceMail default value is displayed to my own number if it is true</string>
    <string name="config_timeZoneRulesCheckRetryCount">The number of times a time zone update check is allowed to fail before the system will stop
         reacting to reliability triggers.
         [This is only used if config_enableUpdateableTimeZoneRules and
         config_timeZoneRulesUpdateTrackingEnabled are true.]</string>
    <string name="config_timeZoneRulesCheckTimeMillisAllowed">The allowed time in milliseconds between an update check intent being broadcast and the
         response being considered overdue. Reliability triggers will not fire in this time.
         [This is only used if config_enableUpdateableTimeZoneRules and
         config_timeZoneRulesUpdateTrackingEnabled are true.]</string>
    <string name="config_timeZoneRulesUpdateTrackingEnabled">Enables APK-based time zone update triggering. Set this to false when updates are triggered
         via external events and not by APK updates. For example, if an updater checks with a server
         on a regular schedule.
         [This is only used if config_enableUpdateableTimeZoneRules is true.]</string>
    <string name="config_tintNotificationActionButtons">Flag indicating that the actions buttons for a notification should be tinted with by the
         color supplied by the Notification.Builder if present</string>
    <string name="config_toastDefaultGravity">Default Gravity setting for the system Toast view. Equivalent to: Gravity.CENTER_HORIZONTAL | Gravity.BOTTOM</string>
    <string name="config_triplePressOnPowerBehavior">Control the behavior when the user triple presses the power button.\n
            0 - Nothing\n
            1 - Toggle theater mode setting\n
            2 - Brightness boost</string>
    <string name="config_ui_enableFadingMarquee">Enables or disables fading edges when marquee is enabled in TextView.
         Off by default, since the framebuffer readback used to implement the
         fading edges is prohibitively expensive on most GPUs.</string>
    <string name="config_undockedHdmiRotation">The number of degrees to rotate the display when the device has HDMI connected
         but is not in a dock.  A value of -1 means no change in orientation by default.
         Use -1 except on older devices whose Hardware Composer HAL does not
         provide full support for multiple displays.</string>
    <string name="config_unplugTurnsOnScreen">If this is true, the screen will come on when you unplug usb/power/whatever</string>
    <string name="config_usbChargingMessage">If this is true, the message that USB is only being used for charging will be shown</string>
    <string name="config_useAttentionLight">Set this true only if the device has separate attention and notification lights</string>
    <string name="config_useDefaultFocusHighlight">Whether the device uses the default focus highlight when focus state isn\'t specified</string>
    <string name="config_useDevInputEventForAudioJack">When true use the linux /dev/input/event subsystem to detect the switch changes
         on the headphone/microphone jack. When false use the older uevent framework.</string>
    <string name="config_useFixedVolume">Flag indicating that the media framework should not allow changes or mute on any
         stream or master volumes</string>
    <string name="config_useRoundIcon">Flag indicating whether round icons should be parsed from the application manifest</string>
    <string name="config_useVideoPauseWorkaround">When true, indicates that the vendor\'s IMS implementation requires a workaround when
     sending a request to enable or disable the camera while the video session is also
     paused</string>
    <string name="config_useVolumeKeySounds">Flag indicating that the media framework should support playing of sounds on volume
         key usage.  This adds noticeable additional overhead to volume key processing, so
         is disableable for products for which it is irrelevant.</string>
    <string name="config_use_sim_language_file">Flag to indicate if EF LI/EF PL should be used for system language</string>
    <string name="config_use_voip_mode_for_ims">Whether to use voip audio mode for ims call</string>
    <string name="config_user_notification_of_restrictied_mobile_access">Flag indicating if the user is notified when the mobile network access is restricted</string>
    <string name="config_virtualKeyQuietTimeMillis">Specifies the amount of time to disable virtual keys after the screen is touched
         in order to filter out accidental virtual key presses due to swiping gestures
         or taps near the edge of the display.  May be 0 to disable the feature.
         It is recommended that this value be no more than 250 ms.
         This feature should be disabled for most devices.</string>
    <string name="config_voice_capable">Flag indicating whether the current device is "voice capable".
         If true, this means that the device supports circuit-switched
         (i.e. voice) phone calls over the telephony network, and is
         allowed to display the in-call UI while a cellular voice call is
         active.  This can be overridden to false for "data only" devices
         which can\'t make voice calls and don\'t support any in-call UI.
         Note: this flag is subtly different from the
         PackageManager.FEATURE_TELEPHONY system feature, which is
         available on *any* device with a telephony radio, even if the
         device is data-only.</string>
    <string name="config_volte_replacement_rat">If Voice Radio Technology is RIL_RADIO_TECHNOLOGY_LTE:14 or
         RIL_RADIO_TECHNOLOGY_UNKNOWN:0 this is the value that should be used instead.
         A configuration value of RIL_RADIO_TECHNOLOGY_UNKNOWN:0 means
         there is no replacement value and that the default assumption
         for phone type (GSM) should be used.</string>
    <string name="config_wifiDisplaySupportsProtectedBuffers">Set to true if the wifi display supports compositing content stored
         in gralloc protected buffers.  For this to be true, there must exist
         a protected hardware path for surface flinger to composite and send
         protected buffers to the wifi display video encoder.
         If this flag is false, we advise applications not to use protected
         buffers (if possible) when presenting content to a wifi display because
         the content may be blanked.
         This flag controls whether the {@link Display#FLAG_SUPPORTS_PROTECTED_BUFFERS}
         flag is set for wifi displays.</string>
    <string name="config_wifi_active_rx_cur_ma">Rx current for wifi radio</string>
    <string name="config_wifi_associated_short_scan_interval">Integer indicating associated partial scan short interval in milliseconds</string>
    <string name="config_wifi_background_scan_support">Boolean indicating whether the wifi chipset supports background scanning mechanism.
         This mechanism allows the host to remain in suspend state and the dongle to actively
         scan and wake the host when a configured SSID is detected by the dongle. This chipset
         capability can provide power savings when wifi needs to be always kept on.</string>
    <string name="config_wifi_batched_scan_supported">Whether Wifi driver supports batched scan</string>
    <string name="config_wifi_disconnected_short_scan_interval">Integer indicating disconnect mode short scan interval in milliseconds</string>
    <string name="config_wifi_dual_band_support">Boolean indicating whether the wifi chipset has dual frequency band support</string>
    <string name="config_wifi_enable_disconnection_debounce">Boolean indicating we re-try re-associating once upon disconnection and RSSI is high failure</string>
    <string name="config_wifi_enable_wifi_firmware_debugging">Boolean indicating whether or not wifi firmware debugging is enabled</string>
    <string name="config_wifi_fast_bss_transition_enabled">Boolean indicating whether 802.11r Fast BSS Transition is enabled on this platform</string>
    <string name="config_wifi_framework_associated_full_scan_backoff">Integer indicating associated full scan backoff, representing a fraction: xx/8</string>
    <string name="config_wifi_framework_associated_full_scan_max_interval">Integer indicating associated full scan max interval in milliseconds</string>
    <string name="config_wifi_framework_associated_full_scan_max_total_dwell_time">Integer indicating associated full scan max total dwell time in milliseconds</string>
    <string name="config_wifi_framework_associated_partial_scan_max_num_active_channels">Integer indicating associated full scan max num active channels</string>
    <string name="config_wifi_framework_current_network_boost">Integer indicating RSSI boost given to current network</string>
    <string name="config_wifi_framework_enable_associated_network_selection">Boolean indicating associated network selection is allowed</string>
    <string name="config_wifi_framework_enable_voice_call_sar_tx_power_limit">Boolean indicating whether framework needs to set the tx power limit for meeting SAR requirements
         during voice calls</string>
    <string name="config_wifi_framework_max_rx_rate_for_full_scan">Integer specifying the max packet RX rates for full scan</string>
    <string name="config_wifi_framework_max_tx_rate_for_full_scan">Integer specifying the max packet TX rates for full scan</string>
    <string name="config_wifi_framework_min_rx_rate_for_staying_on_network">Integer specifying the min packet RX rates in packets per second for staying on the same network</string>
    <string name="config_wifi_framework_min_tx_rate_for_staying_on_network">Integer specifying the min packet TX rates in packets per second for staying on the same network</string>
    <string name="config_wifi_framework_scan_interval">Integer indicating the framework scan interval in milliseconds. This is used in the scenario
         where the chipset does not support background scanning (config_wifi_background_scan_suport
         is false) to set up a periodic wake up scan so that the device can connect to a new access
         point on the move. A value of 0 means no periodic scans will be used in the framework.</string>
    <string name="config_wifi_framework_scan_result_rssi_level_patchup_value">Integer indicating how to handle beacons with uninitialized RSSI value of 0</string>
    <string name="config_wifi_idle_receive_cur_ma">Idle Receive current for wifi radio</string>
    <string name="config_wifi_logger_ring_buffer_default_size_limit_kb">Integer size limit, in KB, for a single WifiLogger ringbuffer, in default logging mode</string>
    <string name="config_wifi_logger_ring_buffer_verbose_size_limit_kb">Integer size limit, in KB, for a single WifiLogger ringbuffer, in verbose logging mode</string>
    <string name="config_wifi_network_switching_blacklist_time">Integer indicating amount of time failed networks are blacklisted for the purpose
         of network switching in milliseconds</string>
    <string name="config_wifi_no_network_periodic_scan_interval">Integer indicating the framework no networks periodic scan interval in milliseconds</string>
    <string name="config_wifi_only_link_same_credential_configurations">Boolean indicating that wifi only link configuratios that have exact same credentials (i.e PSK)</string>
    <string name="config_wifi_operating_voltage_mv">Operating volatage for wifi radio</string>
    <string name="config_wifi_revert_country_code_on_cellular_loss">Boolean indicating whether or not to revert to default country code when cellular
         radio is unable to find any MCC information to infer wifi country code from</string>
    <string name="config_wifi_scan_interval_p2p_connected">Integer indicating wpa_supplicant scan interval when p2p is connected in milliseconds</string>
    <string name="config_wifi_supplicant_scan_interval">Integer indicating wpa_supplicant scan interval in milliseconds</string>
    <string name="config_wifi_turn_off_during_emergency_call">Boolean indicating whether or not wifi should turn off when emergency call is made</string>
    <string name="config_wifi_tx_cur_ma">Tx current for wifi radio</string>
    <string name="config_wifi_wakeup_available">Controls the WiFi wakeup feature.\n
          0 = Not available\n
          1 = Available</string>
    <string name="config_wimaxEnabled">Sets and Unsets WiMAX</string>
    <string name="config_windowEnableCircularEmulatorDisplayOverlay">Default value for whether circular emulators (ro.emulator.circular)
         should show a display overlay on the screen</string>
    <string name="config_windowOutsetBottom">Override this value if the device has a chin, i.e. area that is not actual part of the
         screen but you would like to be treated as a real display. The value is the height of the
         chin.</string>
    <string name="config_zen_repeat_callers_threshold">Priority repeat caller threshold, in minutes</string>
    <string name="db_connection_pool_size">Maximum number of database connections opened and managed by framework layer
         to handle queries on each database when using Write-Ahead Logging</string>
    <string name="db_default_idle_connection_timeout">The number of milliseconds that SQLite connection is allowed to be idle before it
         is closed and removed from the pool</string>
    <string name="db_journal_size_limit">Maximum size of the persistent journal file in bytes.
         If the journal file grows to be larger than this amount then SQLite will
         truncate it after committing the transaction.</string>
    <string name="db_wal_autocheckpoint">The Write-Ahead Log auto-checkpoint interval in database pages (typically 1 to 4KB).
         The log is checkpointed automatically whenever it exceeds this many pages.
         When a database is reopened, its journal mode is set back to the default
         journal mode, which may cause a checkpoint operation to occur.  Checkpoints
         can also happen at other times when transactions are committed.
         The bigger the WAL file, the longer a checkpoint operation takes, so we try
         to keep the WAL file relatively small to avoid long delays.
         The size of the WAL file is also constrained by \'db_journal_size_limit\'.</string>
    <string name="imsServiceAllowTurnOff">Flag indicating whether the IMS service can be turned off. If false then
        the service will not be turned-off completely (the ImsManager.turnOffIms() will
        be disabled) but individual Features can be disabled using ImsConfig.setFeatureValue()</string>
    <string name="skipHoldBeforeMerge"> Flag indicating apps will skip sending hold request before merge. In this case
        IMS service implementation will do both.i.e.hold followed by merge.</string>
    <string name="skip_restoring_network_selection">Boolean indicating if restoring network selection should be skipped.
        The restoring is handled by modem if it is true</string>
    <string name="status_bar_notification_info_maxnum">Maximum numerical value that will be shown in a status bar
         notification icon or in the notification itself. Will be replaced
         with status_bar_notification_info_overflow when shown in the
         UI.</string>
    <string name="config_LTE_RSRP_threshold_type">Flag indicating whether strict threshold is used, or lenient threshold is used,
          when evaluating RSRP for LTE antenna bar display\n
           0. Strict threshold\n
           1. Lenient threshold</string>
    <string name="config_allowAutoBrightnessActiveDozeLightSensor">This flag enables light sensor sampling while dozing. A single sample is taken upon
         entering doze mode, and another sample is taken every time the display enters STATE_DOZE
         or STATE_DOZE_SUSPEND. It is recommended that config_dozeSensorLuxLevels and
         config_dozeBrightnessBacklightValues have entries so that the doze mode brightness can be
         determined dynamically.</string>
    <string name="config_carrier_volte_provisioned">Flag specifying whether VoLTE availability is based on provisioning</string>
    <string name="config_useNewSensorSamplesForDoze">This flag should be used with config_allowAutoBrightnessActiveDozeLightSensor set to true.
         The screen brightness of a device is based off of a ring buffer of the last n seconds of
         ambient light sensor sample readings.
         If this flag is true, then this buffer is cleared every time a new sample is taken in doze
         mode and the screen brightness is based off the new reading. This mode may be better suited
         for watches.
         If this flag is false, then this buffer is untouched.</string>
    <string name="config_wifi_hotspot2_enabled">Boolean indicating whether Hotspot 2.0/Passpoint and ANQP queries is enabled</string>

    <!-- System UI -->
    <string name="carrier_network_change_anim_time">Duration of the full carrier network change icon animation</string>
    <string name="config_alwaysExpandNonGroupedNotifications">Whether or not notifications that can be expanded will always be in their expanded state.
         This value only affects notifications that are not a group of notifications from the same
         applications. If this value is false, then only the first notification will be expanded;
         the other notifications need to be manually expanded by the user.</string>
    <string name="config_chargingFastThreshold">Threshold in micro watts above which a charger is rated as "fast"; 1.5A @ 5V</string>
    <string name="config_chargingSlowlyThreshold">Threshold in micro watts below which a charger is rated as "slow"; 1A @ 5V</string>
    <string name="config_clipNotificationScrollToTop">Whether or the notifications should be clipped to be reduced in height if it has been
         scrolled to the top of the screen</string>
    <string name="config_clipNotificationsToOutline">Whether or not the notification contents should be clipped to any background that is
         set on the notification container. For example, if this value is true and the background
         has rounded corners, then the contents will be clipped to those corners.</string>
    <string name="config_drawNotificationBackground">Whether or not a background should be drawn behind a notification</string>
    <string name="config_enableFullscreenUserSwitcher">Whether to show the full screen user switcher</string>
    <string name="config_enableKeyguardService">Whether to enable KeyguardService or not</string>
    <string name="config_enableNonGroupedNotificationExpand">Whether or not an expandable notification can be manually expanded or collapsed by the
         user. Grouped notifications are still expandable even if this value is false.</string>
    <string name="config_enableNotificationShadeDrag">Whether or the notifications can be shown and dismissed with a drag</string>
    <string name="config_enableNotificationsClearAll">Whether or not the button to clear all notifications will be shown</string>
    <string name="config_enableShadowOnChildNotifications">Whether or not child notifications that are part of a group will have shadows</string>
    <string name="config_fadeDependingOnAmountSwiped">Whether or not the fade on the notification is based on the amount that it has been swiped
         off-screen</string>
    <string name="config_fadeNotificationsOnDismiss">Whether or not the notifications should always fade as they are dismissed</string>
    <string name="config_hideDividersDuringExpand">Whether or not the dividing lines should be shown when the container is expanding and
         collapsing. If this value is true, then the lines will only show when the container has
         been completely expanded.</string>
    <string name="config_hideLtePlus">Should "LTE"/"4G" be shown instead of "LTE+"/"4G+" when on NETWORK_TYPE_LTE_CA?</string>
    <string name="config_hspa_data_distinguishable">Control whether status bar should distinguish HSPA data icon form UMTS
        data icon on devices</string>
    <string name="config_inflateSignalStrength">Whether to artificially interpret all signal strengths as
         one bar higher than they actually are</string>
    <string name="config_keyguardShowCameraAffordance">Show camera affordance on Keyguard</string>
    <string name="config_keyguardUserSwitcher">Set to true to enable the user switcher on the keyguard</string>
    <string name="config_lockscreenAntiFalsingClassifierEnabled">If true, enable the advance anti-falsing classifier on the lockscreen. On some devices it
         does not work well, particularly with noisy touchscreens. Note that disabling it may
         increase the rate of unintentional unlocks.</string>
    <string name="config_maxNotificationIcons">How many icons may be shown at once in the system bar. Includes any
         slots that may be reused for things like IME control.</string>
    <string name="config_notification_snooze_time_default">Snooze: default notification snooze time</string>
    <string name="config_notifications_round_rect_clipping">Whether to clip notification contents with a rounded rectangle. Might be expensive on
         certain GPU\'s and thus can be turned off with only minimal visual impact.</string>
    <string name="config_recents_fake_shadows">Whether to use cheap, less good looking shadows for recents</string>
    <string name="config_recents_max_icon_count">The number of app icons we keep in memory</string>
    <string name="config_recents_max_thumbnail_count">The number of app thumbnails we keep in memory</string>
    <string name="config_recents_use_hardware_layers">Whether recents should use hardware layers for its taskviews. This flag can be enabled
        for devices where the java drawing of round rects may be slow</string>
    <string name="config_show4GForLTE">Should "4G" be shown instead of "LTE" when the network is NETWORK_TYPE_LTE?</string>
    <string name="config_showActivity">Whether to show activity indicators in the status bar</string>
    <string name="config_showDividersWhenGroupNotificationExpanded">Whether or not there should be dividing lines between child notifications when the
         group has been expanded</string>
    <string name="config_showGroupNotificationBgWhenExpanded">Whether or not a view containing child notifications will have a custom background when
         it has been expanded to reveal its children</string>
    <string name="config_showMin3G">When true, show 1/2G networks as 3G</string>
    <string name="config_showNotificationExpandButtonAtEnd">Whether or not to show the expand button at the end of the notification header</string>
    <string name="config_showNotificationGear">Whether or not the gear icon on notifications should be shown. The gear is shown when
         the notification is not swiped enough to dismiss it.</string>
    <string name="config_showNotificationShelf">Whether or not to show the notification shelf that houses the icons of notifications that
        have been scrolled off-screen</string>
    <string name="config_showPhoneRSSIForData">Show phone (voice) signal strength instead of data in mobile RSSI</string>
    <string name="config_showRotationLock">Show rotation lock toggle in System UI</string>
    <string name="config_showTemperatureWarning">Whether to show a warning notification when the device reaches a certain temperature</string>
    <string name="config_statusBarShowNumber">Whether or not we show the number in the bar</string>
    <string name="config_status_bar_scrim_behind_use_src">Whether we should use SRC drawing mode when drawing the scrim behind. If this flag is set,
         we change the canvas opacity so libhwui doesn\'t call glClear on our surface, and then we
         draw the scrim with SRC to overwrite the whole buffer, which saves us a layer of overdraw.
         However, SRC performs poorly on some devices, where it is more efficient to
         glClear + SRC_OVER, in which case this flag should be disabled.</string>
    <string name="config_translateNotificationContentsOnSwipe">Whether or not the parent of the notification row itself is being translated when swiped or
         its children views. If true, then the contents are translated and vice versa.</string>
    <string name="config_vibrateOnIconAnimation">Should we vibrate on an icon animation of the shelf. This should only be active if the
        vibrator is capable of subtle vibrations.</string>
    <string name="config_warningTemperature">Temp at which to show a warning notification if config_showTemperatureWarning is true.
         If &lt; 0, uses the value from
         HardwarePropertiesManager#getDeviceTemperatures - config_warningTemperatureTolerance. </string>
    <string name="config_warningTemperatureTolerance">Fudge factor for how much below the shutdown temp to show the warning</string>
    <string name="days_to_show_color_inversion_tile">Color inversion tile: number of days to show after feature is used</string>
    <string name="days_to_show_hotspot_tile">Hotspot tile: number of days to show after feature is used</string>
    <string name="doze_display_state_supported">Doze: does this device support STATE_DOZE?</string>
    <string name="doze_double_tap_reports_touch_coordinates">Doze: whether the double tap sensor reports 2D touch coordinates</string>
    <string name="doze_pickup_performs_proximity_check">Doze: can we assume the pickup sensor includes a proximity check?
         This is ignored if doze_pickup_subtype_performs_proximity_check is not empty.</string>
    <string name="doze_proximity_check_before_pulse">Doze: check proximity sensor before pulsing?</string>
    <string name="doze_pulse_duration_in">Doze: pulse parameter - how long does it take to fade in?</string>
    <string name="doze_pulse_duration_in_pickup">Doze: pulse parameter - how long does it take to fade in after a pickup?</string>
    <string name="doze_pulse_duration_out">Doze: pulse parameter - how long does it take to fade out?</string>
    <string name="doze_pulse_duration_visible">Doze: pulse parameter - once faded in, how long does it stay visible?</string>
    <string name="doze_pulse_on_notifications">Doze: should notifications be used as a pulse signal?</string>
    <string name="doze_pulse_on_significant_motion">Doze: should the significant motion sensor be used as a pulse signal?</string>
    <string name="doze_small_icon_alpha">Doze: alpha to apply to small icons when dozing</string>
    <string name="doze_suspend_display_state_supported">Doze: does this device support STATE_DOZE_SUSPEND?</string>
    <string name="enable_volume_ui">Enables/disables the default volume dialog</string>
    <string name="heads_up_default_snooze_length_ms">Milliseconds after a heads up notification is pushed back
        before the app can interrupt again</string>
    <string name="heads_up_notification_decay">Milliseconds before the heads up notification auto-dismisses</string>
    <string name="heads_up_notification_minimum_time">Minimum display time for a heads up notification, in milliseconds</string>
    <string name="keyguard_max_notification_count">The maximum count of notifications on Keyguard. The rest will be collapsed in an overflow
        card.</string>
    <string name="long_press_dock_anim_duration">Animation duration when using long press on recents to dock</string>
    <string name="navigation_bar_deadzone_decay">Decay duration (from size_max -> size), in ms</string>
    <string name="navigation_bar_deadzone_hold">Decay duration (from size_max -> size), in ms</string>
    <string name="notification_panel_layout_gravity">Gravity for the notification panel</string>
    <string name="one_finger_pop_duration_ms">The length of the vibration when the notification pops open</string>
    <string name="quick_settings_brightness_dialog_long_timeout">Long timeout for brightness dialog to disappear</string>
    <string name="quick_settings_brightness_dialog_short_timeout">Short timeout for brightness dialog to disappear</string>
    <string name="quick_settings_num_columns">The number of columns in the QuickSettings</string>
    <string name="quick_settings_num_rows">The number of rows in the QuickSettings</string>
    <string name="quick_settings_num_rows_portrait">The number of rows in the QuickSettings</string>
    <string name="quick_settings_rssi_tile_capitalization">Whether or not the RSSI tile is capitalized</string>
    <string name="quick_settings_user_time_settings_tile_span">The number of columns that the top level tiles span in the QuickSettings</string>
    <string name="quick_settings_wide">Whether QuickSettings is in a phone landscape</string>
    <string name="recents_alt_tab_key_delay">The delay to enforce between each alt-tab key press</string>
    <string name="recents_animate_task_stack_scroll_duration">The animation duration for scrolling the stack to a particular item</string>
    <string name="recents_auto_advance_duration">The animation duration for scrolling the stack to a particular item</string>
    <string name="recents_grow_in_multiwindow">In multi-window, determines whether the stack where recents lives should grow from
         the smallest position when being launched</string>
    <string name="recents_nav_bar_scrim_enter_duration">The min animation duration for animating the nav bar scrim in</string>
    <string name="recents_subsequent_auto_advance_duration">The animation duration for subsequent scrolling the stack to a particular item</string>
    <string name="recents_svelte_level">Svelte specific logic, see RecentsConfiguration.SVELTE_* constants</string>
    <string name="recents_task_bar_dismiss_delay_seconds">The duration in seconds to wait before the dismiss buttons are shown</string>
    <string name="recents_task_enter_from_affiliated_app_duration">The duration for animating the task decorations in after transitioning from an app</string>
    <string name="recents_task_enter_from_app_duration">The duration for animating the task decorations in after transitioning from an app</string>
    <string name="recents_task_exit_to_app_duration">The duration for animating the task decorations out before transitioning to an app</string>
    <string name="scaled_password_text_size">The size of PIN text in the PIN unlock method</string>
    <string name="touch_acceptance_delay">Milliseconds before the heads up notification accepts touches</string>
    <string name="volume_expand_animation_duration">Duration of the expansion animation in the volume dialog</string>
    <string name="zen_mode_alarm_warning_threshold">Number of times to show the strong alarm warning text in the volume dialog</string>
    <string name="zen_mode_max_conditions">Maximum number of total conditions to display in the zen mode selection panel</string>
    <string name="config_alwaysShowMultiUserSwitcher">Whether or not the multi-user switcher should be visible even if the quick settings are
         not expanded. If there are not multiple users on the system, the switcher will still
         hide itself.</string>
    <string name="config_enableQuickSettingsOverscrollExpansion">Whether or not the quick settings should be revealed on an overscroll of the
         notifications panel</string>
    <string name="config_showQuickSettingsEditingIcon">Whether or not the edit icon on the quick settings header is shown</string>
    <string name="config_showQuickSettingsExpandIndicator">Whether or not the expand indicator is visible for manually expanding the quick settings
         panel</string>
    <string name="config_showQuickSettingsRow">Whether or not to display the row of quick settings icons separate from the full quick
         settings panel</string>
    <string name="doze_pickup_vibration_threshold">Doze: duration to avoid false pickup gestures triggered by notification vibrations</string>


</resources>
